<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Revision-Notes on Chenyang‘s page</title>
    <link>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Revision-Notes on Chenyang‘s page</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Mining Review Note</title>
      <link>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/data-mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/data-mining/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This material covers key points of BBU6504: Data Mining.&#xA;Note Some parts of material are adapted from the BBU6504 lecture slides and is intended for personal study and educational use only.&#xA;Lecture1: Introuction What is Data Mining?&#xA;KDD - Knowledge discovery in database&#xA;GET unknown and potentially useful information from data&#xA;Exploration &amp;amp; analysis, by automatic or semi-automatic means, of large quantities of data in order to discover&#xA;Attribute Type Ordered Differences Meaningful True Zero Ratios Valid Nominal No No No No Ordinal Yes No No No Interval Yes Yes No No Ratio Yes Yes Yes Yes Noise For objects, noise is an extraneous object For attributes, noise refers to modification of original values</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Leaning Final Revision Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/ml_revision/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/ml_revision/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This review note is madeI made this material as a final review note for QMUL Module CBU5201: Machine Leaning. It covers key points and some most difficult parts of this module.&#xA;Tutorial I voluntarily conducted two 2-hour online tutorials to help students preparing for resit exams, in response to an initiative by the school. This material was created for that purpose.&#xA;Note Some parts of material are adapted from teaching slides of CBU5201: Machine Leaning, especially some screenshots of those slides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Science and Technology: Survival Guide</title>
      <link>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/guidance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/guidance/</guid>
      <description>Todo This blog will be completed after the final exam to give a survival guide for IST based on my personal experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Law Final Review Note</title>
      <link>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/ai_law_revision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/ai_law_revision/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I made this material as a final review note for QMUL Module EBU5107: AI Law. It covers key points from Teaching Block3(AI and Intellectual Property) and Block4(AI and Privacy&amp;amp;Security).&#xA;Note Some parts of material are adapted from the EBU5017 lecture slides and is intended for personal study and educational use only.&#xA;Download Block3 Note.pdf</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My paper for CUMCM2024</title>
      <link>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/cumcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/cumcm/</guid>
      <description>I participated in the 2024 China Undergraduate Mathematical Contest in Modeling(CUMCM) and won the national second prize.&#xA;Our team&amp;rsquo;s winning paper is attached here for reference.&#xA;You can visit the website of Haitong Lan (https://haitonglan.github.io/)(my friend and my teammate), to get more information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Circuit Design Final Revision Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/rea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lcy412.github.io/revision-notes/rea/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I made this material as a final review note for QMUL Module EBU4202: Digital Circuit Design. It covers key points and some most difficult parts from Teaching Block1——Block3. Block4 is not included due to time limit.&#xA;Tutorial I hosted and ran the tutorial on June 11, 2024 from 7:30 PM to 9:30 PM to help BUPT-QMUL students review the course Digital Circuit Design. The tutorial was for students from two majors, which are Intelligence Science and Technology and Electronic Information Engineering.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
